all men get to this age now i don't know
if women ever get to this age
let me let me see uh of course you're
not there you're not there
i can't tell if you're there you're
there
and this guy you've been there for a
while
now what age am i talking about i'm at
the age
i'm starting to make noises
when i don't want to make noises
if i do any kind of work around the
house i make two noises one noise when i
do the work
and then another noise is about a second
later and it sounds like i'm
thinking about the work that i just did
now i'll show you and you'll get it
watch this okay ready
here we go
are we all on board that's the whole
joke right there
everything two noises i move a lamp a
mouse a little floor lamb
[Laughter]
i make noises doing almost nothing
sitting down i come home at the end of
the day i sit in my chair at the end of
the day
have you ever sat down made a noise and
have people concerned for your
well-being after you make the noise
are you okay are you all right i'm fine
thank you very much
i got my butt all the way back thank you
you know i won't tell how old i am you
know it's actually bad luck in show
business
to reveal your age to an audience but
i'll tell you this
i recently purchased a bed and the bed
came with a 20-year warranty
and as i paid for it i'm thinking to
myself this is my deathbed
[Laughter]
so i'm getting a pillow top
i deserve it
i make noises doing almost nothing
adjusting the thermostat in the living
room
how much work is a thermostat a dial
on the wall a little dial sounds like
i'm dragging a piano across the room
yeah yeah yeah
uh
man i love doing jokes and i do my
thermostat bit
and you laugh because that means you
know what a thermostat is it's like
these are my people i'll do that joke in
manhattan and get no response
because they all live in apartments with
radiators they don't know what a
thermostat is i better explain to
audiences like
in manhattan what thermostats were like
there were children
like there were little children gathered
at my feet all right all right listen up
listen up
no no no scoot forward story time
outside of cities they live in houses
yes they do they really do
inside their houses they have a choice
as to what the temperature is going to
be
it's like science fiction
because you've never lived in an
apartment with a radiator not a lot of
minute
temperature adjustments and radiators
radiators are on
or off in the winter you can either
comfortably hang raw
meats in the living room or you're
running into your hallway on
fire
the only way to adjust the temperature
and apart where the radiator is
open the window we have a landlord here
ladies and gentlemen
they raise and lower the window to
adjust the amount of the arctic air mass
they're going to let in
honey it's getting toasty time for a
nor'easter
this guy is kind of funny i hope it is
i'm in a friend's apartment i'm in a
friend's apartment
he's adjusting the temperature with the
window see so as a joke i take a magic
marker
on the edge of the window i just rode in
76 74.
that's funny right that's fine i call
that a brooklyn thermostat that's a
brooklyn thermostat
when i work up in canada uh i have to
adjust that joke
because during the celsius scale you
know uh because canadians are very
you know canadians are very earnest
they're good people but they take what
you say literally
right i remember there i'm going 78 76
canadian guy stands up
you're gonna kill him that's too hot
doesn't mean no you'll burn them up
they're going to burn out
what kind of a man are you
[Laughter]
i love canada my only problem with
canada is they're coins
canadian coins come down and live
amongst us
i don't know you folks if i get a
canadian quarter in my change
my day is shot
because for the rest of the day it's
like i'm a kid i'm playing tag and i'm
it
because i'm trying to give it to
somebody else
sometimes you get a canadian quarter and
you don't know you got it so it goes in
your pocket you won't see it all day
you're going to buy something you're
reaching your pocket for what you think
is a regular quarter
and you get this other thing and
they're deceptive same
size and the same weight but they have a
different picture
in your mind they'll try and justify it
oh my gosh i just noticed apparently
george washington was a transvestite
my father my dad my dad used to make the
same noise
when he'd adjust the thermostat in our
house only then he'd look over his
shoulder i mean my dad used to go
uh they look over at me
they go back that thermostat i think he
thought i was somehow hooked up to the
thermostat
and if they got the temperature right
i'd become the sun he wanted
there you go that should do it right
there no that ain't gonna do it
[Applause]
[Music]
local man robs wendy's with alligator
for the alligator boys now and the later
they sent them to the bank should be
going mom
[Music]
mom